all right everybody
we are live you are back it is the jack
murphy live podcast this
is jack murphy you can find me on
youtube at jack murphy live you can find
me on twitter jack murphy live
at the website jackmurphylive.com the
book is democrat to deplorable go to
amazon
pick that up today the best explanation
of what happened in 2016
and probably a great explanation of
what's gonna happen here in 2020
and today i have with me the one and
only amanda milius we've known each
other now for a couple of years
and i got to tell you uh i was surprised
to find out some of your lineage some of
your heritage all the background and
everything because we just got
introduced and we were just hanging out
and it was great but amanda here
has uh just released or is about to
an amazing powerful important movie a
documentary called the plot against the
president
amanda is the writer and the director
and she's here with me today amanda
how you doing hey how's it going thanks
for having me jack
it's awesome to see you on the uh the
interwebs
versus hanging out at all the hangouts
like we do
we did we spent many a time in the trump
hotel uh
at the various events all around town
and random backs of
of ubers and cruising across the city i
mean we've had some really fun times and
to be honest like i said i had no idea
uh who your father was what you were up
to film-wise
you know at the time you were just uh
working for
the administration so why don't we start
with that amanda how did you end up in
washington what were you doing
give us a little bit of background on
that um well
actually the way i got into the
administration was i
i was touring a movie um because i'd
gone to usc film school
did a a short to graduate and i was
touring that movie around
uh film festivals it was in like 40
different film festivals this is when i
was trying to go the normal
hollywood route and i was like the
culture wars the only thing that matters
i was still very political but i was
trying to be
um i was going very like andrew
breitbart uh
dc is downstream from hollywood so i was
like okay i need to do culture war stuff
and i was kind of undercover like i mean
most people i knew knew that i was
republican
but um so i'm so i'm touring this movie
and uh and i had all this time off
because i'd be three weeks
traveling and then three weeks off so i
was kind of doing odds and ends and i
was getting so caught up in the election
because it was 2016.
uh i was with the president since the
escalator speech like i was i was
obsessed
since like 2015. and uh
and then so i ended up um joining the
campaign as a volunteer i was drive out
to vegas
in my off weeks and just live in this
crappy little motel
and volunteer at the head office there
in nevada
and then as the election got closer and
closer they hired me
and i started assisting the attorneys
and
doing the debates and like just doing
all this i just got sucked into it
and then somebody said to me you know
why are you going to sign up to work in
the administration when we win
and i was like oh don't be silly they're
they're not who's going to let me in the
government i'm like have you met me
that's not going to
no one's gonna let me do that like
that's not what i thought
and they're like no that's what we need
we need people who have no experience
in dc but who believe in the president
and the agenda and the mission
and can bring something new to the table
and so i was like huh
okay like that's that that makes sense
and so i i
signed up i got hired at first the
inaugural committee
um which is you know the committee that
plans the inauguration which is like
planning
10 super bowls in one month it's really
intense but actually coming from a
production background it's kind of
useful
because you're used to planning big
events with lots of moving parts
so uh so then i did that and then i got
hired uh for the administration
as a point d at the state department and
what i was doing at the state department
was actually i was the deputy assistant
secretary
for content which means i was making you
know we
talked a little bit amongst ourselves
about information warfare
so that's not exactly what we do we tell
the truth and we explain american policy
and we explain the administration's
policies but i was i was in
the head of the department that made the
content that would explain
to the foreign audience what we were
doing in the united states
and that was an awesome job and i think
i went really well i did that for three
three years maybe three and a half yeah
so i was in the whole time
um and uh and then this movie
kind of faithfully fell into my lap
and i realized i was like i think i'm
the only person that can do this i mean
not to
you know i'm not like tooting my own
horn or whatever but i don't think
there's any other filmmakers in the
administration
i don't think that there's anybody else
that has the background that i did
and so knowing the players that i did in
this
film in the book by the book i mean the
the film based on lee smith's book
uh the plot against president same name
um
i saw it in manuscript form and i
optioned it right away
and before it even came out it was big
bestseller and it was just
uh it was just off and running from
there well you do
have background your family has
background in film so this isn't
something
totally off the wall for you like you
said you went to film school but
we got to talk a little bit about your
dad because i want the guys to know who
are listening the audience to know and i
want to have a special
connection here so tell tell the viewers
who your dad is and
and what your sort of hollywood lineage
is here
uh my dad's name is john millius and he
is he was a really prolific writer
uh in the 70s 80s and 90s he was also a
director
he wrote apocalypse now and he wrote and
directed
red dawn conan the barbarian the wind in
the lion
he wrote dirty hairy um
and uh a scene well the the um thing a
lot of people like is the um
um the uss indianapolis scene in jaws
uh for steven spielberg which was pretty
cool and then um
he's just he was oh he wrote rome which
was the hbo series
um and he just was you know
this was a time when you could be i mean
okay he still had tension for being a
conservative in hollywood this was not
like no one noticed every single article
about him is like crazy
conservative even though he was the most
professional prolific writer
and an amazing director they have to
preface everything with oh he's
got guns you know i mean you're going
forward to the nra
um they actually based this is funny
they actually based the character walter
sobcheck on him
um in the big lebowski and we didn't
know that when we were
we were growing up kind of we saw it and
my brothers and i were like
that is weirdly like dad like have you
noticed that that character is like i
mean it's exactly like dad and then we
found out that that was because
it was actually based on him that's
incredible that's incredible so i
am gen x square gen x and i remember
red dawn and first of all i believe it's
a piece of trivia may have been the
first pg-13 movie ever released i
remember that
and then of course the whole story is a
group of kids rising up to defend the
country from foreign invaders
and the rallying cry wolverines is
something that me
and all my friends we yelled out we
played the games in the backyard when
kids still played
you know cowboys and indians or whatever
let's go play guns you know so we did we
played guns
and we screamed out wolverines and we
defended our neighborhood from the
foreign invaders and
it was so great so there is a little
fanboy in me right now just pleased that
i'm connecting indirectly here with the
energy and creator of that film
and what's what's interesting uh to know
is like those
movies have very strong masculine energy
yeah and and there is a dearth of
masculine energy today and in fact
me and my mission my guys my whole
audience liminal order where
we really believe that masculinity may
be the antidote to
what is ailing this country today and so
uh there's a really nice sort of uh
congruence here for me
to talk to you talk about your dad talk
about the masculine representations in
the movies that he made
and then to think actually i was
thinking just the other day
you know we need a red dawn today
something that is artistic that but is
valuable that tells a story that
rallies masculine energy and and sort of
uh
nationalism and a sense of like we have
to come together to fight something
that's invading us
because we are being invaded right now
we're invaded by ideas
ideology we're invaded by people uh in
our own government that hate us that
want to end us that don't want to see
any masculine energy don't want to see
any masculine leadership
and so this is a really nice sort of
context
to understand now this film that you
have made
that really is outlining the threats
that we are facing and we're gonna get
into
the content of the movie um but i'm also
interested
in sort of like how did it happen what
was it like
you know when did you decide to make the
movie um
what was it like getting together the
cast of characters the production
team etc so you know why don't you like
tell us just sort of how this came about
so that we can understand like you're
working in dc
working for state you know you know all
these people have you been replanning
this the whole time like tell us the
genesis
and and the timeline and really you know
what guys want to know how do you make a
movie you know like
let's talk about it i i mean i don't
advise doing it as quickly as we did
because that's
absolutely not the way you do it um oh
and
really quick on the dad thing for you
for your guys hold on wait
here's my poster there oh there it is it
wasn't just for this show that sits
there
in a place i i always have that um
because really i think you're right that
movie
motivates the time period we're in now
we all do kind of need that
um that burst um and
uh that that spirit we've lost the
american independent spirit in movies
and music
everything's completely corporate
everything's washed down everything is
uh really made for an international
audience that's the biggest problem is
that you've got
china um reviewing everything hollywood
does which means it's never going to
appeal
exactly to americans into that spirit
that rebellious independent spirit
which is really important and they
absolutely are trying to just kill
masculinity in movies
which by the way is bad for both men and
women because
there's not no women don't want
unmasculine
men wandering around like whatever i
just i don't understand who this
benefits but it's not anybody
uh and then also weirdly on that note so
right before i left um right before i
left film school i know i was on the
film school i was gonna write this piece
i had this piece then i couldn't the
place i was going to run it didn't run
it but
my dad never gets mentioned is this but
you know how these days they're obsessed
with like women
tough women in film and they always have
some stupid
character doing kung fu out of nowhere
who's like beating up all the guys
and it's completely not believable and
it's just annoying and the characters
just really
irritating and annoying and it's there's
nothing there's nothing really like that
likable about them finally my dad
actually had
the strongest female characters as well
in his films if you look at it the girls
in red dawn
they were freaked out and they
complained but eventually they picked up
the guns and they fought alongside
everybody else and they were actually
really cool and pretty bad badass
and then you've got uh valeria in conan
the barbarian who is
probably the best female character ever
i mean ever and then you've also gotten
wind in the lion there's
um mrs pedicares who's like you know
she drives the guy nuts she's super
tough with a sword
she kills people but it's not in this
like annoying
way she's like an actual woman it's it's
actually
it's an interesting thing i was if i was
going to stay in film i would have done
more with that
but anyway um sorry onto your no we can
dig down on this for a second
you grew up in the filmmaking family did
you know you were always going to get
into film i mean you went to film school
but like was that just a default choice
were you excited about it
now yeah i mean it's really just by
default
i can't i can't i have no other skills
doubtful
no but um uh yeah i was around it all
the time and so it's something you think
about it's like um
i used to say when they'd ask you you
know bubble blood nepotism in hollywood
whatever
and i'm like nobody complains about
nepotism in the coal mining industry
where they're like your dad worked in
the coal mine how dare you by the way
you got
a really good job in the coal mine and
frankly if my parents worked in coal
mining i would probably be like you know
i mean that's
the likelihood of you doing what is
around you is very high
so um you know it's not like i'm like in
the coppolas or something where like
their goldfish came out with their
directorial debut
debut i mean everybody in that movie
makes movies it's insane that family
makes movies
but good for them you know they got a
legacy um but it's like
uh of course that's what i'm gonna do
because i'm around it
the time as i said at the time i thought
i wouldn't do it is because the politics
got so bad
and being right wing at all like forget
even being like a you know really big
social conservative which i don't i
don't really think i am i think i'm more
of like a political
trump conservative right um
it's impossible so i i figured when i
joined the administration that i had
just kind of like
like threw a grenade into my career that
i just
spent a lot of time cultivating and
going to film school and i was like i
just can't be right i can't do this like
i have to join politics it's too
important
and then the fact that this movie landed
um
it really it really just all came
together it was like this
faded thing even the people that i
worked with
it was it was like a faded situation
where i was like i have to make this
movie
even if i didn't want to i was like i
have to make this movie like this is
i'm the only one that's going to be able
to do this um obviously not taking like
all the credit like the team
did it and it was as i said based on lee
smith's book who had the idea
to base the story on people
and their discovery of the russia gate
crimes as opposed to just
documents and declassified information
and and this kind of dry like you know
um new breaking news kind of way it was
actually through these amazing
characters like that's the thing is the
the people that discovered this devin
nunes cash patel jack lang or
rick grinnell like i mean these people
are just so vibrant and
have such cool stories that i think that
was really um
that's what you can make a movie about
yeah yeah so
uh everything starts with a story and if
you gotta have a good story and good
characters and good arcs and
interesting people and uh you mentioned
cash cash was my favorite
uh you know he may be younger than me so
it's like this weird thing to like
see somebody younger than me but who's
so wildly competent and successful and
like but yet
you can still hear it in their voice and
like some of the words they're just like
wow young people these days they can
really get some things done i don't know
how old the guy
is but i enjoyed his segments quite a
bit because he seemed pretty fearless
and i
i loved what he did and we're gonna
we're gonna get to all that for sure but
um interesting that you went to film
school with that
he steals the show no he really did yeah
like the uh
he he becomes the star and i think he's
what people really identify with for
exactly what you're saying
a he's not a known figure you don't see
him on fox news every day
and b he approaches this just like we
all would approach it which is
i picked up the dossier i looked at it
and i was like this is [ __ ]
like this is so obvious like and he just
does the obvious
he's like okay well we can prove this
wrong really easily here's what we do
and because he's fearless he's still
fearless i mean the guy
um you know he says he's like we just
got to keep winning
and it's a it's a total great attitude
to have
yeah i felt some resonance with him
because just like me
uh in my sort of media information
career here i've just started pulling on
a string and asked questions and man
but 10 years later i'm still pulling on
the same damn string trying to figure
out what's going on our culture what's
going on our politics
and he read this thing he's like this is
stupid we got to figure this out there's
simple questions we can ask
and he started to ask them and
especially of 65 people which we're
definitely going to get to because
that was a huge unbelievable moment that
i didn't necessarily know of but again
i'm going to push that down the road
just a little bit i just want to wrap
this up your context
you know you grew up in a hollywood
family your dad's wildly accomplished he
made
movies that that represent a certain
perspective in politics and and culture
and then you end up in in the campaign i
did not know that you were there at the
escalator that's awesome
oh i wasn't the escalator but i i was um
on board on board at that time escalator
time
yeah yeah so so you're on board very
early then you come to dc you do all of
your dc work you read this book you're
in manuscript form
and yeah you are the perfect person to
do it you you you knew
all these people already uh you run in
all these same circles and you
understand the content you understand
the city and you understand how to make
a movie so of course
is a very natural fit it must have
seemed like a very logical thing to do
and in fact you're saying it's like
you had no other choice you were
compelled i mean it seemed logical
except for the fact that i had a
government job
uh every day seemed like an emergency
in the government where i was like i
can't leave and go make a movie i have
to do
you know i got to do this this and this
like who will do it if i leave and
uh like and you're just like okay uh
somebody explained it best to me
um because i was freaking out i was like
am i really gonna leave
uh and go start my own company and make
a movie that's gonna
have me targeted by you know i'm gonna
make enemies out of
all of the people that tried to take
down the president like i'm like that's
kind of big um and uh and as a friend of
mine said to me he was like
cause i was like should i do this if i
do this i gotta resign like really quick
and a friend of mine said um what are
you gonna do you're gonna spend the next
uh next year beating your head against a
wall
um arguing with uh bureaucrats trying to
change the phrasing of two or three
sentences in like a un
statement are you gonna go make a movie
that could change the world and i was
like
well okay
i was like i guess i was like all right
i guess i should probably go try
at least um yeah you know i didn't know
if we're gonna be able to do it the
timeline is insane
uh you know and it's hard to explain to
people that don't
make movies that you're like you can't
there's certain things you can't it's
not about
leisurely taking my time and thinking
about it and having like artistic
moments
you physically cannot make that many
interviews
edited together into something coherent
that fast
um you know the first cut of the movie
was four and a half hours long we have
70 hours of footage
we did 35 interviews in a month and a
half which
by the way is insane and um
yeah so we'll probably release the long
version uh the four and a half hour
version in like eight little parts like
a series
we're probably going to do that on one
of the platforms that's coming soon um
so that people can kind of dive into the
section that they're most interested in
whether that's the investigation
the flynn background which i think is
really interesting
um the media stuff i mean each of these
has their own
place uh kind of in the story
yeah indeed there's several segments but
they're all tied together with the same
basic
theme and the same basic theme is that
the democrats were afraid they were
scared
they didn't want mike flynn to come in
mike knew where all the skeletons were
he was also operating on a very advanced
level
in terms of intelligence action and
restructuring the way the intelligence
network works
which is a very fourth generation
warfare where you push down
push down intelligence analysis and
decision making into the field
make intelligence distribution
horizontal rather than vertical
intelligence has become an industry
sorry not to i told you i was going to
jump in like crazy
intelligence has become an industry and
that's the scariest thing is not only
are they disgustingly corrupt and need
to be completely dissolved and rebuilt
from scratch because there's no saving
them
and that's how i feel um but um and they
can come
do whatever they want like everyone's
afraid of them they're like they're a
bunch of pencil pushing dorks like i
don't who cares um
but uh but the other thing is uh they've
become an industry them and that we
people
frequently know about like the defense
uh you know the military industrial
complexes you whatever you want to call
it
but the intel industry is also
ridiculous and so when you've got
because we look at this these like what
flynn was trying to do which is make it
more
um immediate actionable which is
actually what keeps us safe like they
always hide under this banner of like
but we're keeping america safe and
you're like how is you being in my phone
keeping america safe i don't i don't
believe you anymore sorry
like you don't have my trust anymore you
lost it um and it's
it's not uh yeah it's so so what he was
trying to do and what when we talked to
kt mcfarland and
um who was his deputy and uh people like
michael anton and his uh
you know a lot of people that he worked
with um
describing what he was gonna do
basically
he had he had the crime of thinking that
they were too bloated and that we needed
to cut down some of their positions it's
the same reason why the swamp is after
donald trump
um that's what i use flynn as in the
movie flynn is like a
um a through line and a microcosm an
individual microcosm in a way of
the the bigger picture of what they're
trying to do to the whole administration
and donald trump
and his ideas in general like this town
is so nasty if you try to shrink it
there is one thing you can't touch i
mean it's like you can do all kinds of
things
but if you try and shrink their stupid
buildings and their
ridiculously bloated programs if you try
and mess with that they will
come for you it's it's like pock work
well what's beautiful about that
is to see that donald trump delivered
on his promise to cut out waste abuse
and corruption okay that's what every
candidate says it's something very easy
to say
like i've said it when i got hired to be
executive director of various
organizations ceo it's like yeah we're
going to go after waste fraud and abuse
it's a catch phrase and then you find
out that it's really hard to go after
waste from
abuse especially on these entrenched
bureaucracies that have been around
have have spanned multiple different
administrations
held multiple different generations even
and when trump first appointed
his various cabinet members they
went out with the idea of shrinking the
freaking
government man state department you must
know very well
i mean the problem is then you get in
with um
which now i can say which is that a good
portion of the people that are even in
the administration
uh even at the highest levels have zero
interest in shrinking the government and
are doing a terrible job at it some of
them are doing okay and pretty pretty
great and we
that's that's great um but then you get
this other situation not to go too nutty
on the bureaucracy thing but i
i i have ptsd from working bureaucracy i
got to tell you
but so um the other thing that happens
is i notice what they do is they find
these lower level political appointees
and they isolate them and they go okay
this is like the highest most she she
job this person's ever had
we're going to roll out the red carpet
for them give them an assistant
fly them around on the united states
plane
um take them all over the world and and
treat them like
royalty at these embassies and roll out
the carpet as though there's some
important dignitary and so many of these
appointees even if they
if they're just kind of on the fence
like bushy's or
um you know your average kind of rnc
person that comes in if they're not
hardcore magga
they come in and they see that and
they're like oh
i'm not actually going to cut this
program because i want to go
to um brussels and have and speak at the
conference and stay at the nice hotel
and and i'm i'm part of the atlantic
council now and
oh i'm i'm i'm doing cooperation with
europe and blah blah blah blah and
you're just like no you're supposed to
ask all of this like the fact that like
i'm probably i think i'm banned from the
atlantic council headquarters because of
what i
did when i went there but that's what
you're supposed to do if you're a trump
appointee
and you're invited into the cfr you
messed up
like you messed up you're not helpful
you're not youthful they buy them off
or you get these bushies that are just
selling out the administration right and
left like
don't even get me started but yeah it's
uh it's really annoying
so at least he tried a little bit but
what's
interesting to hear you say and this
highlights a very difficult problem that
we've been facing is that
not only trump was elected as an
insurgent as a weapon to go in and
disrupt the uniparty and the
corporatists and the globalists and we
all know the story by now
and yet he's constantly battling
internally his opposition within the
government
deep state entrenched bureaucrats
whatever you want to call it the
institutions
and now you're telling me that even of
his appointees of which there were it
was troubled
staffing right they couldn't staff up
but even if some of the appointees and i
know you've got some names in mind we're
not going to kill anybody today but i
know you know some people in mind
because i can see you like telling
somebody's story as you're describing
some
some general vague person i couldn't
even pick just one
i mean and so we're learning now that
then
even the maga appointees not really maga
and you know we have a bunch of mutual
friends some still in the administration
and we constantly are talking about like
how many of us are there
and like there's really not that many so
let me ask you a question
how many of us are there in the
administration who actually have
power to do things to implement the
agenda or to advise
advising you know trump and his team
on sort of the cutting edge ideas like
4g warfare and other things that we all
know about
like what like is there is it is it
smaller number than i think am i going
to be terrified
it's really small i mean to be fair just
to to be a little bit
balanced i'd say that you know i'm not
miss everything i didn't i wasn't
interacting i wasn't in the highest
levels of this that or the other
i was in my lane i was at state
department i know state department
inside and out
i know the parts of the white house that
i know and a handful of the other
agencies you know some agencies were
better than others frequently you'd hear
about
commerce being like the pl like if you
were to mega for any other agency they'd
go hide you with commerce you'd be fine
but um but that all had to do with
whoever the secretary was
um the amount of us that there are is in
us us um is very small um
i usually say you can crown it on one
hand because
you've got a situation where once they
figure out that you're actually mega
the people around will just stab you in
the back and do anything to keep you
from getting to like a higher position
of power
i think the only reason that i survived
being
as fully mega as i was is because
i'm the only person that could have done
my job again because there are no other
content creators in the administration
there are no other there's no who's
gonna who's gonna do my job who's gonna
run content for the united states like
what some guy that's like done press
releases for the navy like that's
i mean bless him but that's not gonna
happen like you don't know how to make
videos and make things you're compelling
and convince people of things
just it doesn't exist so i i think i got
lucky there and i landed in the position
that i needed to be in
but the um you know i mean it's
at this point i've been out for six
months
um what happened right before i went out
is something really important which is
the ppo which is presidential personnel
office got
really good like um something happened
and there was a shift
and uh suddenly the hiring got a lot
better
and we got a lot more mega people in so
i have a feeling it's much better now
um i think that was a change that
happened a couple months before i had
left
uh but you know that was in the last
year again we need another four years
because we our first term
was spent battling imaginary
russians and uh ukrainians or whatever i
mean
battling one hoax after another and
filled with um infiltrators
either bushies or whatever and what the
what the bushies do which is what we
always talk about in in our
in our world we call it you know the
bush league um
they hire each other so you get one of
them in an agency and like there's like
there's some that are okay like there's
people i've known that work for senators
or congressmen that i maybe i don't
particularly like but the per they're
actually really good and they're totally
megan they're they're capable
um but occasionally actually quite a lot
you'll get these bushies
and they'll come in and they'll hire
everybody else from the bush
administration and you're like
you walk into an agency and you're like
what is this who are these people
they're like the architects of the iraq
war and you're like what are you doing
in my state department get out of here
like it's
it's so annoying like i mean you know to
name names for a second like how is
eliot abrams
in our administration like he's
literally
the neocon white walker and he's running
around
running policy like how is that a thing
and so you as a
as a lower level appointee you know
you're kind of like you know you're
trying your best
you're you're pushing the agenda forward
every single day and then you see stuff
like that and you're like
i am now fighting within my own
administration to actually do the
president's agenda
what the hell so we need we need more
time because um
because of that because of so many other
things it's like i can't believe how
many amazing things this administration
has accomplished considering how many
hamstrung
um how hamstrung at times we got behind
the scenes
and in front of in front of the scenes
with with this onslaught of this absurd
hoax
which was crazy from the moment it
happened i mean i remember where i was
when i first heard
this idea of a russia hoax and i and
like devon says in the movie i was like
this has to be a joke
um this can't no one could possibly
think this is real like russia like did
they pull it out of a hat
that they were just like oh we're gonna
pick russia as like the thing like it
made no sense
actually you know what cernovich says uh
we had to there's so much material we've
had to cut out of the movie because it's
like i said couldn't be four and a half
hours long but there's this one great
line that i wanted to keep in but we'll
put it in a promo or something
where he's like you know i wish the
campaign was organized enough to have
been able to uh
collude with russia they couldn't even
collude with themselves
he's like they couldn't even collude
with social media like they were not
they were not colluding with anybody
like lucky they could collude with
headquarters like
uh yeah well on my podcast a few
episodes ago darren beatty he names
names in state department of some
leftovers
uh who even from obama administration
who are
actively working to disrupt uh the
election currently today
uh and it's all over the place and it
really does
uh put some greater context in trump's
achievements
when you realize when the when a regular
average citizen realizes that
we didn't just elect him and he goes to
washington and all of a sudden he's got
full
control and he can implement his agenda
and whatever no he barely even has a
handful of personnel that he can trust
within the entire freaking bureaucracy
and he's fighting from people within the
freaking
gop right first off and then not not
just within his own party and then
within the administration itself within
the bureaucracy and then of course the
democrats
and all the collusion uh that they put
together
they being the only ones that colluded
conspired
cooperated or coordinated with anybody
on this and
i think it's just classic i interviewed
alexander duke the other day
and he was talking about how he had long
advocated for
russia to support all the divisive
elements within the united states all of
the racial antagonism
antifa types black bloc types anything
that they could do to sow
discontent within the united states why
because they didn't believe in the
neocons policy
and like the reagan cold war policy and
so they have
been running information operations in
the united states
forever right like literally forever
uh they were doing it before trump ever
got here they're gonna do it before
after trump is long gone
and actually they're the ones who had an
interest in hillary
you know disrupting things and
supporting black lives matter and all
this stuff so
it seems to me to make sense they're
like yeah you guys are the ones that are
colluding with russia
because we've actually also been
listening to them too
uh fascinating sort of dynamic going on
there
um one thing that really struck me
when we start when you started to
introduce obama was you called obama
you said or he said or somebody said he
brought
chicago style politics to washington dc
now can you explain what that means to
the because i'm from chicago
i know what that means so can you
explain what that means because i
thought that was a very powerful line
that kind of just
kind of just got glossed over a little
bit but i think that's a great example
can you tell us a little bit about that
well the guy so the person who said that
was
actually congressman lee zeldin and you
were talking
in the context of um the motivations
behind
russiagate and uh related to the flynn
um background a lot so
one of the things we're talking about is
is the the preamble to the flynn phone
call
right that people need to understand is
there is there's two
foreign policy related things that
happened right before that phone call
one was
a u.n vote that the obama administration
allowed the united states to abstain
from that condemned israeli settlements
um and you'll see that in the trump
administration quite the opposite
uh the united states takes the exact
opposite approach
it's very very odd for the um
for the for the for the for america to
have done that um
the second one was in order to make the
russian collusion
myth seemed like it had teeth and seem
real
obama kicked out um you know a handful
of russian diplomats
uh and made this whole big big thing
about that
and so what lee was describing was
related to the un
vote about israel and particularly as it
related to the
general flynn's opposition to the iran
deal um okay so
those are sort of your three floating
foreign policy ideas that are behind
there
what they did is
talk about breaking precedent for the
united states they basically
did big foreign policy moves right
before they left the election had
already happened which is important okay
so they were a lame duck a few months
the election had already happened it was
during the transition period between
trump and obama
and they did this huge foreign policy
move to kick
israel in the face and to kick start
hopefully a new cold war with russia
so those are two very very big foreign
foreign affairs
moves to make on your way out the door
usually you kind of leave things
you don't try to start new crap before
the next administration comes in
and so what i think he was referring to
there was both
that style of i would call it petty
um and disruptive but the other thing
he's referring to which i think is
probably what you're referring to which
i witnessed a lot when i worked in the
campaign in nevada
which is the massive corruption which is
the crazy pay for play
politics is a business there everything
is
um greasing hands and and you give me
this and i'll make sure this person's
employed
and you get to run this company and i'm
going to give you 10
of this and oh well by the way we hired
your cousin
i mean it is insane and i i got to be
i've heard that that nevada and and
chicago are the most corrupt
political places probably outside you
know i mean dc and maryland just keep
adding to it but i i have to say i
i that's what i took from it his comment
as well and i
saw that in nevada um you know not to
again not to go on too much of a tangent
but it reminds me because we're
obviously about to have an election
again
when i was in nevada just as like a
lowly uh election
campaign person looking out over the uh
poll watchers and this and that
we had incidents where boxes
of ballots cars driving boxes of ballots
we would find parked in the middle
of dirt parking lots completely isolated
with the doors open and the lights on
and one of our poll watchers would be
like
i was driving you know you're supposed
to be able to accompany uh the car that
takes the ballots and the cartridges
from the polling place to the clerk's
office this is what every
every uh campaign is allowed to do and
we'd have people calling us being like
first of all i was in a car chase they
were trying to lose me which is crazy
and then you you'd have crazy stuff like
that i mean and that's one example we
all night long we were writing down
the wildest stories of like uh
uniformed officers preventing our poll
watchers from entering the clerk's
office
or to see the boxes be unloaded um
intimidation i mean crazy stuff and i've
heard that that
nevada and chicago are like 1930s style
corruption not even really
new corruption it's like like a like a
silly gangster movie
totally totally clark county is totally
full of corruption
in my book democrat to deplorable still
available on amazon.com by the way
selling very well every month more and
more every month
as more people want to find out what
really happened and why
in my book i i talked to a woman who
worked for the democratic
uh national committee in nevada and she
was a bernie supporter and she was
telling me in our interview that like
bernie's office got shot up like in the
primaries
and i was like that can't be right and i
did a little bit of research what do you
know it was right there in the newspaper
like just people shot bullets just into
bernie's headquarters in clark county
in nevada the whole caucus system in
nevada is totally rigged
they stole it all from bernie they
screwed all of the delegates they
blocked off the parking lots they
blocked off the entrances
they like started the meetings early
changed the rules dragged things out
there was like a riot on the floor
basically uh in clark county and the
caucuses
because the outcome wasn't what it was
supposed to have been so
you combine that with chicago where they
say you know vote early
vote often and everything there is
about exactly bribes which was uncovered
you know many years ago
uh all throughout chicago with the daily
family and everybody going on there so
it was just interesting to me that
comment it touched me being from chicago
and it just adds to the milieu right
that milieu
of what trump is walking into he's
walking into obama and chicago style
politics he's walking into
uh you know the the administration his
own administration is fighting him the
gop that is fighting him
everybody in town fighting him and
before he even gets there
they decide to unleash an information
warfare operation and i'm going to go on
just a little bit of a tangent here but
then i want to dig into this concept
because look
people ask if there's a civil war afoot
people ask if there
is going to be a conflict i'm telling
you folks we are already
in the middle of that civil war it's
just that it doesn't look the way you
expect it to look earlier generations of
warfare involve people lining up across
the field and shooting muskets at each
other then eventually it's you're in
like
trenches with artillery and then
eventually you're with
tanks moving very quickly and
outmaneuvering people
but now now it's everywhere it's all
encompassing it's a moral
level it is on a mental level it's on a
physical kinetic level
it happens in the media it happens in
your mind it happens with information
and we're being controlled now through
information and these information
warfare operations
which interestingly enough general flynn
knows plenty about
and here we are we walk into this and
they unleash what is
perhaps i mean very effective certainly
very powerful and totally egregious and
disgusting
operation that was unleashed on the
american people so let's put it in that
frame
okay information warfare operation this
is what was kicked off
let's take us through the story let's
start getting into the meat of things
what is an information warfare operation
how did it get started here
and what are what are we talking what
are the moving parts and and how
have hillary obama and the democratic
national committee and the rest of them
colluded they're the collusion
people they're the conspirators they're
the ones that cooperated on all this to
make this happen these crimes this hoax
let's start let's get into the mechanics
what what is the main thrust here
i mean i think the best there's a
there's a lot of people that speak about
that exact thing in the film and one
person in particular is john
solomon and he talks about how
america itself so you spoke about the
the um the fomenting of the fractures of
american society that was taken
advantage of
earlier the other aspects of that is
that the united states itself has very
advanced
information warfare techniques obviously
there's things i certainly don't know
there's things
that that ever you know what i mean like
it's it's clearly we're very good at
this
um what he talks about is that the tools
that were used by nsa
cia state department dod
etc etc um
clearly were used against the american
people here
um and that's really scary
so now we're not only at risk from
foreign governments but basically
certain parts of our own government
when they decide that we don't vote for
the right person are going to
abuse the public with a three or four
year long hoax
combined with a second hoax about
ukraine combined with god only knows
what now
i mean they're doing the exact same
thing that they were doing before
now the the audacity of the fbi
to do that unsourced leak if if that's
what happened
about how hunter biden's laptop is
russian disinformation
is the craziest thing i i mean i can't
even believe they have the audacity to
do that after everyone
already knows that the russiagate thing
was a hoax
i mean i say that but everybody doesn't
know that there's still plenty of people
walking around thinking that
the trump administration campaign um or
campaign had anything to do with russia
it's like it's still a thing they've
they've won at it because
basically it's it's so much um
easier to have a coup and to have
warfare when it's
information based and they've been doing
it for a really long time
otherwise you look at things um like
totalitarian countries
where everybody's under control because
of um
uh kind of um in your face um
fear and uh um
it's like a more overt sense but imagine
how much easier it is to just pull a
hoax over on everybody
put it out on the national on the media
that's why i that's why i go after the
media so much in this movie
is because none of this would have been
possible without the media's being
complicit
like the cia could have done whatever
they want fbi could have done whatever
they want but it wouldn't have worked on
the entire public
if the media wasn't out there pushing it
saying exactly what they were saying and
lying to us every single day
and um that's really dangerous they've
destroyed their own institutions
um the information warfare aspect of it
is it's it's really the scariest part
because it's really hard to fight
it's really really you have to have i
mean if it wasn't for and
again another reason why i include
people in the film like mike cernovich
jack the soviet
um or journalists like john solomon
people that got it right um because
the mainstream media looks down their
nose at them and poo poos them and is
like oh they're just these internet
personalities
and and you've got these high and mighty
ivory tower
people that think they're the only ones
that can write about foreign policy and
they're the only ones that can tell us
the news and they were wrong and they've
been wrong
for 25 years it's not new they've always
so the idea that um these voices exist
that's why they're clamping down on us
so hard that's why you know
the twitter blackouts happen the way
they do shadow banning
the tech companies being the oligarchs
that they are working directly with
china and shutting us all down i mean
it's like um america it's you know what
it is bringing it back to red dawn
yes wolverines um
but that's what a lot of patriots
thought the war was gonna look like and
they were like i'm ready
i got you know i'm a prepper i've got
i've got
my my you know stock i've got my my
you know i'm i'm ready for the war when
the war comes i used to joke about that
i'd say because you know my mom is
actually a
um a really good uh um she's like a
champion
um shotgun shooter um which is
she's just like my dad she's an actress
she's in hollywood but she's
very very um pro-gun very republican
anyway so um but like i was always like
oh god when the war comes my mom's gonna
be ready she's like stockpiling water
and got like the you know
target practice and da da da but that's
what people thought it was going to look
like they thought it was going to look
like red dawn
they thought we were going to be like
taking positions behind rocks and firing
at an incoming enemy or a government
that was out of control
that's not what's going to happen it's
already happening just like what you
said they're just
going to pull a hoax over on everybody
you're going to see it on your tv
um the one guy actually besides john
solomon who's
amazing on this issue um
is edward uh dr ludwak who uh is uh he
wrote the book coup d'etat
and he explains how in a democracy this
is what a coup
looks like you don't see the kind of
coup like you would see
in um in africa or places in south
america
where there's an you know there's an
opposing force that comes and takes over
the palace
and then they show up on tv and they say
i'm the president now that's not gonna
happen here what they're gonna do
is you have your secret police right fbi
cia you get your secret police come out
and they go oh my gosh
we found it turns out that the the
current leader
is is a foreign asset and we have to
remove him to save the whole country
and and he really nails that because
that's exactly what happened
and um thank god they didn't succeed but
that's that was information warfare was
saying oh my gosh
you guys happened to have elected you
bad trump people
you elected a russian asset imagine that
and you're like
no i we didn't you just don't like it
because we're going to take
get rid of shrink your stupid
bureaucracy and that's how nasty they
are
i mean it's it's unbelievable but it's
amazing it's amazing how much of it
comes back to just protecting their
money and protecting their position
their status their power
and scoping their crimes that was the
second thing was um
what they're gonna do if you if you
threaten the intel agency's money
there's two things they want their cushy
jobs where they don't they're
unaccountable and the second thing is
is you might find out things that
they've done that make them look
really really really bad and other
horrible lies that they've told us for
the last
god only knows how long probably 40 50
years but so
that's the other thing is they've got uh
and john o'connor explains that really
well who is
um was a deep throats
lawyer who from watergate which he's
fantastic at explaining this
um but he explains it in that it was a
defensive and an offensive measure
because they're they're getting us away
from their their budget so we don't mess
with their bureaucracies
and they don't have to be accountable to
anybody and by the way
they have a lot of crimes to cover up so
of course they want to distract
everybody with pretend
other crimes and the mueller
investigation that discovered nothing
except for the fact that we were all
right
but um yeah so this is
this is why mike flynn became such a
target right so mike flynn was former
head of dia
mike flynn is a sort of younger
generation of general one who
understands fourth generation warfare
one who understands the way the
intelligence information should flow he
not only
knew the crimes but he also had a
different vision for the way that the
military and intelligence
structures of the united states should
be should be structured
and that threatens big budgets it
threatens the big defense contractors
because
we don't really need a million guys with
rifles on the ground
what we need are targeted operations
media operations information operations
special special operations stuff it's a
much more smaller scale
and you know he was going to change the
way things worked
he had an idea we talked about this with
michael anton
and even in talking with anton a few
episodes ago
it just makes me really shake my head
and just and just
wish and wonder what would have happened
if anton
and and um and flynn and bannon even
had stuck around and were able to
continue on the road that they were on
the promises that were made to the
american people um you know
men's people they got chased out by
mcmaster i mean a lot of people they
were expecting me to go harder on
mcmaster in the movie which uh if i had
again there's only so much you can do in
90 minutes
i've made enemies out of everybody else
i could also add hints of the list
but um uh i mean it's it's insane like i
the guy the guy took obama's policies
put them in a new binder and then
pretend tried to pass them off as
as maga as like america first trump
policies and the people that were like
wait a second this is not what we're
supposed to be doing this is stupid
he would chase out of the building and
fire under the president's nose
i mean it's ridiculous um it's
everywhere
we know some of those people we saw it
happen i mean it was insane and then
there was a moment and i'm going to go
back to information warfare here but
just a funny little tangent
there was a moment where mcmaster was
complaining about internet trolls
and leaks and such and we know who he
was talking about
[ __ ] made him the best part and the guy
was like
he literally do you know how many times
i've heard major government officials
walk can i say a bad word on this show
you may okay so i just have to check
because i've been
doing media i'm trying to be good um so
i've been walking around i've been so
much like
more than once i have heard very
high-level government officials say
who the [ __ ] is mike cernovich at that
moment i'm sitting there and i'm like
i don't know never met it makes me so
happy
i love it yeah it's crazy and so you
know people who do not know you know
the there were there were sources and
there was information and and mike did a
very good job of hammering hammering
hammering hammering on mcmaster
and and calling out what they were doing
to personnel and how he was derailing
the trump
uh agenda how he was interfering with
hiring and putting the wrong people in
the right
in the wrong spots uh and uh you know
mike had a had a hand in frustrating him
and hopefully getting him out of there
that's
very interesting yes a couple other
people too
very symbiotic relationship between the
maga new social media universe and the
trump administration
uh jack vasovic being one as well uh
very powerful and influential in that
regard
but back to the information warfare
operation the reason why
it's so powerful is because the first
mover and information
generally wins it's once you can put an
idea in somebody's head
and they're like oh yeah that makes
sense rachel maddow told me so yeah
makes sense
it is very very difficult to dislodge it
no matter how many facts no matter how
much evidence no matter what
an intricate and thorough explanation
you can give to somebody
it is it is an ego attachment because if
you believe
something and you're like okay now i'm
sort of ego invested in this belief
absolutely and then in order to get
someone to let go of that it's
very difficult so if you can even just
get the most outrageous lie into
somebody's head
first carving that thing out is damn
near impossible yeah the person has to
think of themselves as wrong
instead of the two in pieces of
information that are opposing are no
longer neutral
where it's like one is is this one is
that it's it's that whatever one you
attach yourself to
first is you and it's correct and then
in order to even accept the other one
you have to accept that you were wrong
which everyone has a problem with
i'm told i have a problem with that
i'm not so surprised maybe i don't know
why anyone would say that but i've been
told that i
even i have a problem with being told
that i'm wrong so uh
well and so that's why people uh like
that i interviewed for democrat to
deplorable talking about political
transitions
most all of them had to go through a
traumatic experience
something where their belief of the
world
collided with that reality of the world
and nothing added up and you get to the
point where you're just like oh
i just need help like i'm ready for
something new
and absent cognitive dissonance exactly
so absence a traumatic experience
is very difficult to dislodge an idea
from somebody who has taken it in as
their own
and so the the speed by which the
comprehensive nature by which
the multi-pronged approach by which the
democrats and hillary and obama and all
of them put these ideas out into the
zeitgeist pumped them down our brains in
our ears through the newspapers through
cnn
and basically was the first mover and so
from then
oh you're playing defense you're playing
defense from them you're trying to chip
away and chip away
yeah we were playing defense the whole
time and not only that they had the
media they had the media and they had
the government
it's not like we walked into the
administration and all of a sudden all
the bureaucrats and everybody was like
oh yeah you're here
what can we do it was like it was not
like that
so so you had you had situations where
um
where government officials you know
career government officials are sitting
there going
well you're telling me we're doing x y
and z but you're from the trump
administration
and trump is a foreign asset so
therefore i'm not gonna do that i'm
gonna just do my own thing
and by the way i'm gonna spend 2.6
billion dollars
on um you know this new app
that identifies trump people on twitter
as as russian trolls so that we can
silence them
and you're sitting there and you're like
no no hang on a second that's not
reality
that's [ __ ] crazy and you're arguing
with
with senior people do you know how
dangerous that is that they
convinced people in the government that
the president was a russian asset and
that the people that worked for him
were compromised you that's i mean
that's a coup
that is a coup that was going on the
entire time
i mean that's that's what's so crazy and
so you're not just convincing
the general public of this information
warfare
which is bad enough because then what
does that do like
cernovich actually says in the movie
foments violence because
these people can fight in the streets
and that's okay because you're just
fighting russians you're fighting
uh russian assets and nazis and all this
stuff like this
it's insane it's dangerous but then
you're also looking at the governments
you've got your intel people
state department people regular uh
bureaucrats all over and all the
different agencies
second guessing everything about the
administration because they're like well
maybe they're just doing this because
they're pleasing putin
and you're like that isn't stupidest
that you're like it's
it's so dumb but yet so dangerous you
have to take it seriously
um and it's like you said yeah you got
it it's impossible to pry the idea out
of these people's minds i mean one of
the reasons i made the film
um in the way that i did is because
i feel like you would have a hard time
arguing with it there's
there's a lot of conservative films can
be very hyperbolic because conservatives
are so
tired of being silenced and so tired of
not having a movie for them and so tired
of never getting
seeing their vision on the screen of
what they know is true
that um i don't blame them for this but
a lot of times they can go
really far in the hyperbole direction
right like you can you can
throw in a couple of like soaring eagles
with like america the beautiful and you
could say anything like and it's like
well
it's it be it's a it's very preaching to
the choir
i want i hope that i was able to do
something that people can watch
and it's a very well argued movie
and there's you know at first when i was
doing it i was like okay so we're making
some points here that are very important
to get across and i would have two or
three people or four people
saying the exact same thing unprompted i
was in the room this is what i saw
this is what happened this is what the
document said and you know you start
cutting that down because that's that's
though it's a strong argument it's not
the best way to put in a movie but so
i know that it's solid and i think that
comes across in the film
and i feel like um people on the left
people that are skeptics
i think that they would have a hard time
saying that this is hogwash because
how are that many people lying and
and the documents are there i mean
anyway not to go all over them no that's
no it's perfect because you're right the
the movie itself
is not hyperbolic it is not sensational
uh
and you interview prime players
principal actors
people with access in the clearance and
the experience and the action of
actually reading the documents and
putting their reputations on the line
and persevering
after all this time months and months
and years and years
and at putting themselves at personal
risk the
the the slander and the and the libel
and all the defamation
and the [ __ ] that goes out about you
know when when they don't have the facts
and this is what i was going to say to
you what they're going to do to you
when they don't have the facts they go
after
the the messenger and they're going to
you know character assassination
and they're going to and like with with
cash and with nunes and all these guys
they
they they got slaughtered and they got
attacked and people came after them
and when they do that that's a very good
sign that you have the facts
that's what says he goes there's not
that great line that cash sorry the cash
cash has so many good one-liners in the
movie i swear to god
and make t-shirts of him but when he
says when the ass clowns and the media
start uh showing us we know we're over
the target
so true i used to say that when i was at
state department
is i would i would literally run around
and i'd be like why am i not getting any
hit pieces
i am so much more far out like what
where's
like all my friends were being called
white supremacists the nazis and
and and and silly crazy people because
they were you know
miller ally does x and children are in
cages and all this and i'm like i'm
working on immigration policy as hard as
i can why isn't anybody saying where's
my hit piece
but no i was because i see it as a badge
of honor and i mean why
that was the other thing in the
beginning in the trump administration
and this is again exemplified perfectly
by what happened to flynn
if you get a hit piece written about you
in the trump administration there should
be
a six-month period where you can't get
fired because
otherwise the press is running your
personnel office and that's what
happened
for probably two and a half years i mean
at least until the new team came in
if the press wrote a hit piece about you
you'd get some really dorky
head of an agency they'd be like yeah
you know the secretary really doesn't
like all the heat and the bad press and
i'm like well then you're in the wrong
administration
because press isn't gonna like you and
they fired so many good people that way
i mean look what they did to mari stahl
who was one of the most effective
political appointees in the state
department people don't know her name
but she basically stood up for us
um at the un and elsewhere um ambassador
molly who's an amazing person
um i mean look at look at look at what
happened in the white house all the
people that mcmaster chased out
darren beatty is the best example best
example of what was happening darren
beatty should have been preserved in
that administration for life
not fired so um so i mean i was
probably quite lucky that i didn't get
uh get attacked because i knew i work in
the press i know how to fight i
fight but i also i'm not afraid of the
press i'm friends with these people i
talk to them i'm not you know and i can
deal with
it but what i was uh telling somebody
that they're dead i was like so
what's gonna happen is they do they do a
handful of things they either call you
if you're on the right and you're in the
administration you get
cert there's a playbook uh playbook a
is your dumb crazy um
silly not uh educated enough
or whatever you know you're not
qualified option b
is you're a white supremacist or a nazi
option
c is they'll frame you for a crime so
i'm going to go ahead with i know it's
going to be option a because they
already started
and i'm fine with that and like at least
they're not cramming me for a crime
and at least they don't think i'm a
jewish nazi so then we're good we're
good we're
good like whatever if they want to say i
have no education they're totally right
i went to film school and yet i had a
very very high position in the state
department and they can bite me
hey another jewish nazi welcome to the
it's amazing that's the same thing that
happened to me and and uh it's a great
point what mike says
yes now what happened to you is is
interesting because
actually you're an interesting case um i
thought about this i never got to tell
you this
because you got treated like a
government employee
i haven't seen a lot of non-government
administration people
get taken so to the woodshed
by the press and by activists it's weird
because you've got you know it's not
like you're the the only
public maga guy you've got jack pasovic
which of course they they drag him
through everything too
mike they do but they do it to everybody
but i i
i'm hard-pressed to think of somebody
who had really as
me as much real-world damage which i
always meant to mention i i don't
understand that it's very odd
that they really saw you as somebody
they needed to take out
yeah uh i appreciate that yeah you know
at the time i was definitely like a
civilian
i was just hanging out yeah like and
and by civilian i mean not even in the
info war right like
like my social media profile wasn't that
large i didn't do a show like this
didn't have a podcast hadn't written a
book nothing i was just hanging out with
jack and cassandra
and just do like we were just friends
you know and uh yeah they came after me
and it's because of this environment
that you're talking about
where they say that the trump is a
russian asset well actually first they
say it's hitler
then they say oh [ __ ] america voted for
hitler so now we got to say something
else they cheated
right now they gotta change the story so
now they cheated he's a russian asset
and so now they're all nazis they're all
russians and anybody who helped trump
must be a russian must be a nazi so now
it's open season
on regular citizens like i was and
luckily for me
you know i took my beating i got you
know fired i got banned from little
league the whole thing
uh but i decided to take all that energy
jiu jitsu that [ __ ] around turn it into
something positive and here we are a few
years later
now you get a bigger voice now look what
they've done see that's what they do
they don't understand if they don't kill
you
which you know if they don't actually
take you out
you become bigger i don't know why they
don't understand this because
because you have to do what you did
everybody has to do if they take if they
try to take you out you have to go
bigger
you have to just be like okay this is my
career now because otherwise they're
just going to keep doing it i mean i
said this in the administration too
where it was like
you know the one thing i would still say
to the admin
is your press people your sec your
cabinet leaders
you have to protect these people from
the hits from the press if you are
getting hit
by the left-wing press you're doing your
job if you're not
if they're fawning over you then you've
got a problem
you're not doing it right like the fact
that foreign policy i think they called
me um
it was really funny because it was
conveniently they dropped this art
they've never written about me the whole
time i worked in the state department
and it was like
conveniently undoing their precious iran
deal um
uh they uh they didn't have a problem
with me then but then all of a sudden
the movies announced that it's going to
come out and
that day we pushed it a week but that
day october 1st they dropped this story
calling me um the most unimpressive
person
in the trump administration which i feel
is a little hyperbolic i mean
the most unimpressive really like right
like
okay but like you know and you're just
like really
like that that's what they do so i i
realized they're going to go with silly
for me so um yeah discredit discredit
discredit discredit discredit and you
bring up a very good point actually
look we need to understand that we're
not in a conventional warfare mode
and that the trump administration and
anyone that follows in him similar vein
is actually leading basically an
insurgency against the establishment
in the midst of an information war which
means then
that you need to be you need to have
information artillery you need to have
information
warfare coverage you need to have you
need to have like
first aid for your information warriors
and like how are you going to do that by
standing up for them
by sticking up for them by running
counter information operations
not just by being like oh we don't like
the heat you got to get out of here
that's actually a bunch of [ __ ]
yourself from people like when when um
you know when daryn got fired uh from
the administration
um a handful of us i think it was the
next day or a couple days later
we greeted him at the local bar with
with a resounding applause you know
stand by your people a lot of people
will distance themselves because they're
like oh [ __ ] like this is the best job i
ever had like i can't i can't be
associated with so and so
that that is just cowardly like you
cannot do that um you have to stand up
for each other and in social media and
in
the people that are speaking the mag
agenda people that are banned
that's the craziest thing to me how are
we not talking about the people that are
banned do you know like
some of the most entertaining people
from our movement are just gone they're
just memory hold
and and no one talks about them and
you're and and you're supposed to
pretend that they're like these um
you know you're supposed to disavow them
because uh twitter decided that they
weren't okay
i mean it happens to everybody that's
the thing a lot of people went after you
know they kind of made fun of laura
loomer
when she would talk about um getting
banned from uber and all that stuff
guess what i got banned from uber for
life on this movie i haven't heard about
it happening to anybody else like and it
they had some horseshit reason like i
didn't wear a mask for a block and a
half or something but
um this kind of stuff can happen to
everybody
like it's like everybody needs to
just you don't have to agree with the
style of the person but we all need to
be
banding together and standing up and not
in fighting and it's not just
us sort of on the ground or the troops
it has to come from the top so to be
critical of the administration here
if we're in an information war you have
information warriors you have
information
militias rising up right like like you
can really think of like
soba cernovich myself others as info
militia right because we're in a war
it's an insurgency it's an infowar
we have stepped up in absence of federal
power
and like whoa we need to be protected
and that's just by running
cover and running counter ops and
especially for people that are in the
administration and that
along with some of the early hiring
stuff is is part of
you know a reasonable critique of the
presidency
and you know i think that there's been a
lot of lessons learned
over the last few years and really god
willing
the second term will be one where they
understand how to operate in washington
can get some of the right people in
place and maybe start to affect
a greater amount of change and implement
the the trump america first
agenda hopefully we'll see we won't know
what's gonna happen you know
the real maga people in the positions
that
that they ought to be in like we need we
need what we actually here's another
thing
what we need is all over the country
people have to if they can i know not
everybody can but this is how our
country was built
you got to put down your tools put down
your business put down your farm tools
whatever it is
and for the next term you gotta come to
dc
you gotta join the administration and
you have to do your time in government
because
right now 99.9 of the people that work
in government are a lot of them are just
totally fine there's something wrong
with it but they're all democrats so
you're already handicapping any
republican administration because
when a democrat administration comes in
they're all moving downstream they're
all moving in the same direction
we don't have that and um you don't want
people who have been living in
washington forever to be running the
country
like what you can't have that and so
what i realized of course i never wanted
to work in government i
hate the government i don't want to be
in the government so the fact that i
i got kind of you know voluntold to
to join is um is that's a that's a cash
ism too i stole that one
uh um is is great but
uh you know i didn't want to do that
like i was not a nine to five person i'm
i'm creative
uh that's all right i um but that's but
that's so
it's so important i say this to
everybody is it's like
republicans naturally are averse to the
or have an aversion to working in the
government because they're like
like i want to i make money and be my
own thing yes that's true the problem is
you're just going to
have overlords that don't understand
that so
especially the younger uh people that
are getting out of college
um you know join
work in the government for republican
administration for give yourself two
years
you know it could change your life it
could certainly help the country
what's incredible as a longtime resident
of washington dc i will never forget how
the city transformed when obama was
elected okay
when obama was elected all of a sudden
there was just
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
of
new people moved into the city new
government staffers new
ngos staffers new lobbyists new lawyers
new non-profits new think tank people
thousands
tens of thousands of people moved into
the city changed the entire
tenor of the city all new restaurants
all new clubs all new
it changed everything and then the trump
administration nothing changed i know i
didn't notice anything
there's one place where we can hang out
you know we basically know
all right there's we know basically
everybody that moved into dc for the
administration
and so uh yeah that massive change
wasn't there but let's not get too
critical right now because we are
at an important time in american history
we are but just a few
weeks away from the election we can
spend some time critiquing the president
after he wins the election let's stay
focused on the bad bad guys right now
and i want to just do like a real
clinical discussion
of the dnc
fusion steele dossier cnf
fbi cnn fbi like let's talk through that
whole process right there
well the so i think i knew
just enough about russiagate
to tell this movie in a way that people
that don't know the whole detail
um could understand and one of the
things that was the most useful um
for me was when cash and nunes explained
what fusion gps really is
when nunes explains that it's a
racketeering organization it basically
um what they do is you can pay them
to use intel sources to dig up dirt on
people
and by the way everybody has dirt so
it's
it's not like this is just to get to get
dirt on politicians it can be anybody
um and then what they do is uh step one
is publish that information in totally
spun slanted ways whatever makes you
look the worst
and um ideally get people to lose their
jobs ruin their lives whatever it is
that they're
doing that the client of fusion gps
doesn't like
make them stop doing that so there's
that element to it
but they also had another element which
is what really crossed the line
out of being um uh what do they call it
in uh campaign um whatever the thing
they do on
on politicians all the time anyways um
uh contra opposition
opposition sorry my brain's
going uh but so besides being opposition
research um they'll also
feed it into the fbi and that's what
they were doing that's why so many times
people don't understand the nellie or
bruce or connection nelly or being in
fusion being paid by fusion gps
and bruce ohr being in the fbi uh in doj
um being able to feed that information
into law enforcement so not only do you
have hit pieces coming out about you
but guess what you're also framed for a
crime um
and that is un i mean that's that's
that's who these people are that's who
the dnc
through their uh through their lawyer
perk at their their
attorney's office perkins cui um and we
explain this
clearly in in the dock um through them
paying fusion gps to go use british
intel
to go harvest russian disinformation
put it into the press made out of whole
cloth
and then also start an fbi investigation
that's why i'm so angry at the fbi in
these
these um agencies because
it's not like i'm just you know i won't
even get into exactly how i came to be a
right-wing republican kind of person but
it's not like infowars had nothing to do
with it but
um you know i'm already i'm already you
know i've been paranoid about the intel
agencies and about surveillance my whole
life
um you know ask my parents like i've
been a little bit of a nut that way
forever
but i didn't do this you know i didn't
tell them
to become criminals i didn't tell them
to
um produce fake information on a
candidate they didn't like
and and then create false investigations
the fact that they have no credibility
and that most americans hate them
is their fault not mine not the
presidents
not anybody else they ruined their own
institutions
um so yeah sorry i went on a bit of a
tangent there that tends to happen if
you get me talking about the i'm just
i'm so mad at them and i'm so sick of
being quiet about it you know like
people are like well i think the intel
agencies might have a few bad apples
you're like no they're rotten from the
cord just
gone gone gone and they're like oh like
you know who else says that is putin and
you're like
okay uh it's it's so
it's so ridiculous but um i i i yeah
it's the fusion gps thing the fact that
they had anything to do with them
is disgusting and criminal and
um i wouldn't have faith in them to look
into anything i mean a lot look at look
at what we don't know look at
we still have the greatest largest
shooting in american history the las
vegas
massacre we don't know anything about
that but we know
imaginary things about the president and
his associates
that they that they didn't do regarding
russia pp tape we know pp
tape but we don't know las vegas shooter
right that's the absurdity that's
that's it's just information warfare
because it's there's no truth you never
get to hear anything real
that you never you never have any real
investigations it's
just all they are all these agencies are
and the fbi is a tool to assault the
public with fake information to control
people
and get them to vote for whoever you
know do do whatever it is that their
their their interests want now we sound
like crazy conspiracy theorists when we
say this but it's not
it's true and you have tracked it you've
tracked the money
from the dnc into fusion into this
dossier
in the way that it goes to the fbi then
it goes to cnn they talk about it on cnn
then the fbi is like oh they're talking
about it on cnn now we have to have an
investigation
and it's just one big dirty disgusting
loop
that starts with right let's let's be
totally clear
you're talking about so the info
laundering yeah so that's that's that's
the other thing we try to explain so um
what happens there
is they can manufacture an investigation
so
if there's a perfectly neutral person
the fbi as we know digs up dirt on
everybody they've been doing it since
hoover and before and yada yada that's
that's that's what they do
so they they leak something that's
either true and and
spun or completely fake and they leak it
to one of their guys
who we all know who they are some of
them have called me since i've made this
movie hi
how are you go screw yourself um and
um they they leak it to a certain
journalist that they've either planted
at the new york times or the washington
post
um or they just work very closely with
uh and they they leak this
this whatever the nugget is whatever
their little pre-packaged
either it's horseshit or it's real but
they give it to this this journalist
the journalist writes a story based on
the leaked information okay so now we're
at point two
then the story comes out and then the
fbi or the doj in one way or another
uses this story
to make a real investigation about the
person to get
fisa warrants which means warrants to
spy on american citizens
that you don't know you know there could
be a fisa uh that we could we could all
have them on us right now we'd have no
idea
um the uh so they get their little
investigation
um going and then they leak whatever
that whatever
results of such investigation or
whatever they want to say about that
they leak that back to the washington
post or the new york times then the new
york times writes about ooh
investigation about so and so a person's
reputation is ruined
they can't be hired they can't work if
they're in public office they're screwed
like it's it's an and all of that by the
way everything i just described there
doesn't have to be one
instance of truth in any of it there is
no truth there is only information that
was said on my podcast by alexander
dugan the other day
in this very context of information
warfare
right there is no truth there is only
information there is only persuasion
there
that the first mover wins in many cases
because of our ego
attachment to our beliefs yeah it's very
hard to carve these out and then when
you've got
jake tapper cnn
right there you look at him if you don't
if you're a casual observer you're like
this is the most credible man on tv
right jake tapper if you're just a
regular person right
right and there he is talking about the
steele dossier
talking about it with the former
intelligence officials who are now
out who are now doing the rounds in the
media to give it all credibility
work for the media nobody's positive and
like did
i mean they hired the people that lied
to us
for all this time they're all working at
different news organizations and none of
them have had to apologize that's the
crazy thing
if a right-leaning person made that big
of a mistake
they would have to come out and say okay
i made a mistake i'm an idiot
turns out there was no russia collusion
nobody's done that
these guys are still on tv how does
rachel maddow still have an audience
like she's what does she tell them i'm
sorry
i was lying the whole time i couldn't
actually find the smoking gun that i
promised you
night after night after night after
night instead of
review some more pictures of paul
manafort's suits
like what right they just move on they
just move on to the next thing the next
shiny thing the next thing that gets
their attention that's going to be
the new smoking gun the new shocking
evidence the new this is the end of the
trump administration how many times did
we hear that
remember that where they were like the
walls are closing in yeah that's right
that's right
every time and i can't think back i
think back to
uh when um trump uh the the emails were
in question and trump was like
jokingly totally jokingly he's like hey
oh russia you got those emails send them
over
right and then our big secret
communication
he just did it out loud right right i
i read david frum's book just to keep up
with the opposition like
like seriously like it is part of my job
at this point so i read from's book
and the whole thing is all about how
trump is corrupt and uh blah blah blah
russian blah blah
and the linchpin of his argument his
proof
is when trump says hey oh russia you got
them emails send them over
like that was the extent of the proof
that he had and uh it's just
it's i can't i've been doing this um
a little bit with tim poole sometimes
when i'm on a show
we do is it dumb dumb or diabolical
like are these people stupid or are they
actually just malicious negative
evil doers and i honestly i don't know
is it a combination of both i do know
that the whoever kicked off hillary the
dnc
kicked off the steele dossier and the
whole thing
that's evil you know that we know that
was on purpose
um you know who i have to get john
solomon told me this story and this is
totally uh
his his discovery um and this is in his
new book
um which is that the russia
gate story began and i tried to keep
this in the movie but
it's it's it's kind of complex so i part
two
um but so they had the the hillary
campaign had done a poll
um about six months or so before the
russia gate story before the end of the
election they'd done a poll
to see what was hillary's biggest
weakness and it wasn't benghazi
it wasn't some of the things that they
thought it would be it was
her reset button her her selling uh the
uranium
and her her perceived corruption with
russia
so what they decided to do was no matter
who the republican nominee was they were
going to dirty them up with some kind of
connection to russia
because it neutralized the playing field
and
that is how the actual whole thing
started because i always ask myself i
was like
re why russia like why would you pick
that like there's so many
like if i had to put my hat on and be
like well if i'm gonna come up with
something like i'll you know they
obviously tried the women thing that
didn't work
but the russia thing specifically was
actually to inoculate
hillary um who actually has a russia
problem as we've all now seen
and certainly the entire dnc and the
bidens but um
the um but that was a really interesting
piece of information
it's fairly complex but they discovered
this they have that they lay it out
uh john solomon in his book so that's
that's a very um that was pretty
enlightening
yeah and i think it also had a little
bit to do with syria
had a little bit to do with the oil and
gas pipelines and
you know it was very complicated but
actually made a very obvious choice for
them to pick
and you know i forget about that i
forget about hillary's reset
right who's colluding with russia when
you say hey
let's just reset relations and like
uh how about this how about let's just
use logic for a second and say
if putin and the russians really wanted
trump to win
why did they give hillary dirt on trump
like why why why was the dossier all
about bad stuff about trump if you want
the guy to win
why would you give that information to
the opposing to the
the um you know the candidate the
opposite candidate
and it's like the most obvious question
in the world and nobody asks it there's
so many things that have been
memory hold and just twisted because of
the info op
that people aren't even aren't even
questioning i mean the the fact that
the dnc wasn't hacked it was podesta's
emails for one
but you could only say uh that our um
you know the russians hacked our
democracy if you equate
john podesta with our democracy um
and uh a couple handful of other things
that people
don't remember it's all just so absurd
and and one of the most important parts
to remember
is that russia and the united states we
do this too
all the time everywhere in every
election all around the world we
quote metal we have favorites we help
and support people
we have institutions we have organs of
the government
um oh man the name is escaping me right
now um democratic national
national dni i think it's called they
are spaced all over the world
to help to help secure democracy but we
know what that means
it's the agenda to push american agendas
in nicaragua and wherever the place is
all over so like
which those even those okay so let's
pretend for a second that those are
actually legitimate and honest and are
actually trying to push democracy first
of all they're pushing democracy in
places where democracy will not work
because
i'm sorry not every society is the same
and if you don't have
the institutions or the culture to
support democracy like you can rebuild
iraq as many times as you want it's not
going to work
um but i can say that now because i
don't work at the state department
um but uh but i mean what the there's so
we we do all kinds of insane stuff i
mean the stuff that about um
yeah we do we do plenty of things and
that's the other reason why i encourage
everybody to work in government because
otherwise
what's being done in your name as
america
may not be what you think it is like
your version of
spreading freedom and democracy might
look very different by the time it gets
to whatever country
it's being being maneuvered in uh uh you
know than what you would think or hope
right so this idea that the russian
meddling in the uh election
is either true or not or new it's not
it's like it's just it's just the game
dude they have spies all over the
country like
that's how it works and we know that and
we work with them and we're aware of who
they are
and it's just part of the game so
all of this compared to china that's the
other thing it took two years to get the
entire national security apparatus on
board
with what the president said which is an
amazing accomplishment of his by the way
speaking of mentality changes
no one debates whether china is an
adversary at this point
when the president was first campaigning
he would talk about china and all the
press would do is make fun of the way he
said china
if you can imagine that and it's like
now it's very
obvious that this is our biggest um
adversary
and when we started when the
administration started and i i
certainly i think this has been adjusted
but i don't i'm not
100 sure but when we started uh china
wasn't even
uh called an adversary and there's you
know there's like this state department
code of like how you quantify all the
terrible countries in the world and um
and uh and
and they would call china like a
challenge or a a competitor or something
and you're like
no no no they're actually like a full
they're our number one enemy so like you
might want to like update your
stationery that was one of the number
one things that i said that i was voting
for donald trump i wanted him to change
the conversation
around china china is coming for us
they've been coming for us
since longer since the opium wars
they're trying to get revenge on us
they're flooding our country with drugs
the same way we and the brits flooded
their country with drugs in the last
century
they have a long-term plan that operates
on time scales that we cannot fathom
with china is um is they operate on
hundred year plans um and we cannot
think
more than four years in front of our
face because we change you know i mean
that's part of the deal we change
we change government every four years or
every eight years and so the
the strategies and this is one of the
things when i was working in um
the policy planning part of the state
department um
what my boss uh dr kyron skinner was
trying to
emphasize was that we need to be
thinking long term
against china we need to not be thinking
in these four-year chunks
we need to be thinking 50 years out
and and that's that's a really important
thing that that we need to be doing for
our safety yeah
there's been a lot of successes that get
swept under the rug
the china the russia thing was meant to
distract all of us it was meant to
discredit and let's get to the let's get
to the punch line
i want everyone to watch this movie the
plot against the president
first of all let me just say extremely
well done i mean
first rate a plus looks professional the
story flows perfectly the b-roll is
tremendous
all the post-production editing and work
and graphics work
first rate first class there's no
questioning
it's professionalism or how well done it
is it's really really well done
congratulations on that
thank you thank you i have to say i'm
really happy with it i'm amazed
um it could have gone
a different direction considering how
fast we had to do it
and uh the people that worked on it
really pulled it and made it
made it happen um i couldn't obviously
have done it without them and everybody
felt
honored to tell this story and i think
everybody knew that they were really
taking part in a moment in history that
really mattered and
and were willing to do the crazy hours
and and
and pull it off so i i'm really happy
with it
yeah from this from the staff from the
production team to the to
to i don't know what you call people in
a documentary the stars i don't know the
folks that
that were interviewed the prime players
the principal actors
uh all of them with the same
corroborating uh testimony to you
all the same stories just tremendously
well done and i want everyone to go
watch it at p-a-t-p against the
president dot com forward slash watch
now
i believe it is on vimeo it's gonna be
on other outlets as well but go get
it yeah movie dot com just yeah
tpmovie.com okay good p-a-t-p-movie.com
it'll definitely be
in the show notes on here some of the
comments are talking about cash patel
cash patel is fantastic he was my
favorite character because i had not
ever really met him or heard of him
before
and i loved his style and the matter of
fact so like
that's what i wanted to conclude here on
let's conclude tell
tell the story about cash telling the
story about the 65 principles
and the way that they asked them all the
same question and the way that they all
gave the same answer
and we can end on that so that everybody
gets the main freaking point
here which is go for it and explain
um the fact that this wasn't the way
that russiagate was pounded into our
heads
every day for three years this point
should be just as equally pounded into
our heads which is that cash was
on nunes's team that did the
investigation that brought every single
person who would have been involved in
the heads of agencies
in behind closed doors to ask them
under oath he asked every single person
he tells this perfectly
in the in the documentary asked every
single person the same
questions do you have any evidence that
the trump campaign either conspired
colluded or
um cooperated or coordinated one of
those
with the with the russian government
with anybody in the russian government
anybody in the trump campaign and
every single one of them said no and
we're talking about
comey brennan clapper loretta lynch
every single one ever of 65 people they
did 65
or more um interviews and
all of that was what was classified
for so long until the nunes memo and if
you remember a lot of people don't have
time to like watch the news and track
everything the nunes memo
is what revealed that and then beyond
that
when rick grinnell declassified the
actual
transcripts of all of those interviews
they're there
they're all there right now you can go
spend your night reading them
you can go google them and spend all
night long
reading james comey's transcript talking
about how he has no evidence
of russian collusion and the fact that
that is not on every single news channel
blasting all the time i mean it wasn't
not covered
but it wasn't covered in the way that it
should be and a lot of people can't
connect the dots because unless you're
again unless you're like katherine
herridge you know with the with the
documents and everything
she's amazing but you know and and thank
god lee smith the author put this
together
in that clear of a way and thank god
devin nunes and his team
did this and they asked those questions
and you hear cash patel talk about it
when he talks about it he's like
of course we ask those questions because
that's what they were going out on the
media every single night
and they were saying we have seen
evidence of russian collusion
and he even says he goes to schiff and
his staff and he's like are you guys
seeing something
that we're not seeing because we're in
the same hearing we're in the same
briefing i'm not hearing this what are
you what are you talking about
and and then they would just go out on
tv and lie about it
and the other you know so i i recommend
everybody watch it for that because it's
extremely well put by cash
the other thing that was interesting was
congressman mike turner who explains
this other very very very key point
which is if you go into a classified
briefing
and you walk out of the and get
classified information and you walk out
of the classified briefing
and you go to a bunch of reporters and
you tell the truth about what you just
heard
you have committed a crime if you go out
of the classified briefing
and you get this classified information
and you come out and you talk to a bunch
of reporters and you lie
about what you just heard and you tell a
lie you haven't committed a crime
so what he says is these reporters
should seriously ask themselves
how often are these people coming out
committing felonies
about information why like
it's it's just so they're the communi
the media was so
so um um in line to do this
they they so uh conspired with these
with these bad actors to push this hoax
over on the american people for the last
three years
and and frankly the the last part of the
thing that i'll say about really is that
what a lot of the folks say at the end
of the movie you know who benefited our
adversaries
like china and russia couldn't have
asked for
a a better situation to have uh the
american president be doubted
um and for people to be fighting each
other the only winner in all of this was
our adversaries that's what they did
yeah we've been distracted we've been
battling
internecine war within our brothers and
sisters in america
totally just stalling and obfuscating
and ruining momentum and energy and
you're absolutely right it's our foreign
adversaries
that win here and uh it's you know one
of the last points to mention about the
press
i think that many of them many of them
were malicious
but i also think again many of them have
they came out of college
they get their indoctrination they get
come into the media they get more
indoctrination
then they believe the initial lie then
they're all ego invested in
all these things so they're actually
just sort of like
mentally incapable like mentally and
emotionally
incapable of observing reality and
reporting facts in a way that is
even-handed
the everything that they see and do has
to confirm for them
their view that was injected into their
brain
on day one at college orientation about
rape culture and about
intersectionality and racism and evil
and oppression and yada yada
all the way through the process and then
you get out and you're 26
27 and you're covering these things and
it all lines up to all the notions that
have been put in your head
and that's why this war is a total war
it is not just one presidential election
or a conflict with donald
trump this is a total war it starts
at elementary school middle school high
school
college media advertising corporations
sporting events libraries media
everything everywhere is a battlefield
we've all been con conscripted into this
infowar
it's everywhere all the time they're
coming at you whether you want to
participate or not you don't have to
have a uniform on
you don't have to be in the military you
are on the battlefield as it is
and it's in everything that we do so
this election right now is very
important i want trump to win
everybody go out there and vote for
trump please 100
but like it's not going to be over if he
wins and it's also not going to be over
if he loses
this is something that's going to go on
for probably decades
and one of the things one of the vectors
that we need to fight back
is media but his film is even
art so yes my question for you this is
the last question amanda
what are you gonna do next what kind of
art
do you see in your future where is your
oh i just got excited what is your red
dawn
what is going to be your big statement
where are you going to go
you're an accomplished filmmaker now
you've got a great background
you're primed and ready what are you
going to do next
um well considering i just finished it
like
15 days ago i'm gonna kill for a second
and like get my hair done but um
but no i i agree i mean i didn't like i
said i didn't think i was gonna go
back into film i really thought i was
done with it um
it was sort of a good feeling at a
certain point it'd just be like i don't
have to do that again
but now i think i really um one okay one
cool thing that's really happened is my
production company
that i formed just to do this movie has
a ton
of new um projects now on the horizon
there is a
huge appetite for a cool
creative unique um
it's it's not just like it's like only
right wing exactly it's just not
um restricted and corporate and stupid
right it's dissident like i've tried to
explain to people i kind of want this
production company to be like the a24 of
the right but not exactly just of the
right
but but basically like hollywood has
kicked us out and it doesn't they don't
have
um a stranglehold on taste and if
you know i think the other thing that i
think worked out well in this and why i
want to do this production company and
kind of
um i think i'm going to produce for a
while before i direct again
um because that was crazy and that would
i literally
have half nights where i was making this
movie where i was i'm never doing
anything like this again this is insane
but um but uh but no i'm i'm really
interested in some of the projects that
i'm producing under the 1am dc
company and um there's
there's just so much room for really
really good stories
and for tasteful stories and political
documentaries don't have to be
um you know a lot of times i and i
really like this i like that there's a
lot of films being made on the right of
course that's really important and we
all need to support each other and there
need to be more voices not less
um but a lot of times you find like an
advocate of an issue
who's like i'm just i'm gonna go make a
movie about this now
but what we need are actual filmmakers
who are trained and versed in filmmaking
who also happen to have open minds and
and
make movies about the things that they
care about um and i think a lot of it
is the right has traditionally not been
the home of
art for some reason because that's what
the left told us
because during that whole 80s and 90s um
period of time where they would say
things like oh well if you live in the
suburbs you can't be an artist which i
call
some friends and i call it the um edward
scissorhands complex where it's like if
you're unique and different
the suburbs don't like you which is not
makes no
they just created that um but so i think
it's
um it's important for people to to
communicate that way and like i said i
mean andrew breitbart is really the
person that nailed that which is that
um washington is downstream from
hollywood you
change culture before you change policy
and and if we care about our culture
we really really need to do that and i
think it's really important for more
people to get in film
and i hope that my my new little company
can
um can push a lot of things out can put
a lot a lot more
voices out on a lot a lot of new
different platforms fantastic 1am dc i
get it now
am dc 1am i get it i get it
very clever congratulations amanda i
loved
the movie it was sensational uh i think
it's gonna be very well received and
when people
from outside of this universe see it
it's gonna be hard to dismiss
what was in the movie uh congratulations
i know what it's like to give birth
to a big creative project and it's like
oh it's time to chill for a little bit
um welcome back
uh welcome back to the world
again we took the whole crew and we hid
in an undisclosed location so i just got
i'm just happy to be back in uh
in the swamp to continue fighting
nice tell everybody where they can get
the movie yes uh
the best place is a follow us on twitter
uh patp
movie follow us on instagram same handle
and then also go to
uh our website which is p-a-t-p plot
against the president
paddockmovie.com um and we are
constantly updating it with
new platforms where you can see it right
now the best place is vimeo on demand
you can see it on your tv you can see it
on your computer
there are two other platforms listed
there that are free speech friendly
streaming platforms my movies plus
and special project.ios we want to
support them they just launched with
this movie
and it's important to have platforms
because guess what it was also supposed
to be out on amazon
uh four days ago and conveniently
they've decided it needs a longer
content review
uh and they're doing the exact same
thing to dinesh's movie so it's not
about
time it's not about size i have a
feeling it's
i have a feeling like come november 5th
it'll be like oh the movie was
allowed now but so we'll be selling dvds
on our website
go to our website um the we also are in
theaters
we're adding five different we're adding
probably about five or six
towns every week so right now it's in
about six
uh all around the country and we are not
doing the coastal elites first
we are starting in heartland america and
going out
so um tweet at us if you want it in your
town
tweet at everybody who you think needs
to see it um
let's get it out there thank you so much
for having me on
i love your podcast i'm so happy i got
to be on it
thank you amanda i really appreciate it
i loved your movie i'm so glad i got to
talk to you about it
guys i'm jack murphy hit subscribe here
on youtube on this new channel i just
started putting out videos this month
and the response has been tremendous
please hit subscribe here follow me on
twitter jack murphy live get the book
democrats is deplorable also hey keep in
mind i'm going to be on temple again
next wednesday
and then also an election night special
on tim cass
irl so check that out as well thank you
amanda
can't wait to see you again and
congratulations and thank you to
everybody
thank you bye